let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In 1937 which American aviator disappeared while attempting to circumnavigate the globe in flight?",
    answer: "Amelia Earhart",
    options: [
      "Amelia Earhart",
      "Bessie Coleman",
      "Howard Hughes",
      "Jacqueline Cochran"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:2 ,
    question: "Which American actress was found dead at age 36 as a result of barbiturate poisoning, ostensibly self-administered?",
    answer: "Marilyn Monroe",
    options: [
      "Judy Garland",
      "Carole Lombard",
      "Grace Kelly",
      "Marilyn Monroe"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 3,
    question: "Which controversial Russian figureâ€™s assassins attempted to murder him with a combination of poison, gunshots, and drowning?",
    answer: "Grigori Rasputin",
    options: [
      "Joseph Stalin",
      "Vladimir Lenin",
      "Nicholas II",
      "Grigori Rasputin"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb:4 ,
      question: "Which African American explorer was the first known human to set foot on the North Pole?",
      answer: "Matthew Alexander Henson",
      options: [
        "Bart Cubbins, Jr.",
        "Paulson Quintain",
        "Nathaniel J. Moore",
        "Matthew Alexander Henson"
      ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
          question: "What is the name for a central defensively oriented district in ancient Greek cities?",
          answer: "acropolis",
          options: [
            "temple",
            "acropolis",
            "necropolis",
            "Parthenon"
          ]
        },
        {
  numb: 6,
    question: "Which was the most widespread and historically significant writing system in the ancient Middle East?",
    answer: "cuneiform",
    options: [
      "hieroglyphics",
      "papyrus",
      "cuneiform",
      "logograms"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb:7 ,
      question: "Which was the most decorated dog in World War II, winning the Distinguished Service Cross, Silver Star, and Purple Heart?",
      answer: "Chips",
      options: [
        "Gunner",
        "Waxy",
        "Bullets",
        "Chips"
      ]
    },
    {
        numb:8 ,
          question: "In what year did the Western Roman Empire come to an end?",
          answer: "476 CE",
          options: [
            "476 CE",
            "517 CE",
            "1,500 CE",
            "205 CE"
          ]
        },
        {
            numb:9 ,
              question: "Who was a legendary founder of Rome?",
              answer: "Romulus",
              options: [
                "Julius Caesar",
                "Claudius",
                "Romulus",
                "Hannibal"
              ]
            },
            {
                numb:10 ,
                  question: "In 44 B.C.E.,how many time Julius Caesar was stabbed in his assassination? ",
                  answer: "23",
                  options: [
                    "2",
                    "11",
                    "23",
                    "31"
                  ]
                },
                

];